<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<resources>
    <string-array
        name="clemens">
        <item>A banker is a fellow who lends you his umbrella when the
            sun is shining, but wants it back the
            minute it begins to
            rain.</item>
        <item>A man cannot be comfortable without his own approval.
        </item>
        <item>Always acknowledge a fault. This will throw those in
            authority off their guard and give you an opportunity to
            commit more.</item>
        <item>Always do right. This will gratify some people and
            astonish the rest.</item>
        <item>An Englishman is a person who does things because they
            have been done before. An American is a person who does
            things because they haven\'t been done before.</item>
        <item>Barring that natural expression of villainy which we all
            have, the man looked honest enough.</item>
        <item>Be careful about reading health books. You may die of a
            misprint.</item>
        <item>By trying we can easily learn to endure adversity --
            another man\'s I mean.</item>
        <item>Clothes make the man. Naked people have little or no
            influence on society.</item>
        <item>Courage is resistance to fear, mastery of fear - not
            absence of fear.</item>
        <item>Do something every day that you don\'t want to do; this is
            the golden rule for acquiring the habit of doing your duty
            without pain.</item>
        <item>Don\'t go around saying the world owes you a living. The
            world owes you nothing. It was here first.</item>
        <item>Don\'t part with your illusions. When they are gone you may
            still exist, but you have ceased to live.</item>
        <item>Education: that which reveals to the wise, and conceals
            from the stupid, the vast limits of their knowledge.</item>
        <item>Facts are stubborn things, but statistics are more
            pliable.</item>
        <item>Fiction is obliged to stick to possibilities. Truth isn\'t.
        </item>
        <item>Get your facts first, and then you can distort them as
            much as you please.</item>
        <item>Grief can take care of itself, but to get the full value
            of a joy you must have somebody to divide it with.</item>
        <item>Habit is habit and not to be flung out of the window by
            any man, but coaxed downstairs a step at a time.</item>
        <item>Honesty is the best policy - when there is money in it.
        </item>
        <item>Humor is the great thing, the saving thing. The minute it
            crops up, all our irritations and resentments slip away and
            a sunny spirit takes their place.</item>
        <item>I am opposed to millionaires, but it would be dangerous to
            offer me the position.</item>
        <item>I didn\'t attend the funeral, but I sent a nice letter
            saying that I approved of it.</item>
        <item>I don\'t give a damn for a man that can only spell a word
            one way.</item>
        <item>I have a higher and grander standard of principle than
            George Washington. He could not lie; I can, but I won\'t.
        </item>
        <item>I have been through some terrible things in my life, some
            of which actually happened.</item>
        <item>I have never let my schooling interfere with my education.
        </item>
        <item>I have never taken any exercise except sleeping and
            resting.</item>
        <item>I thoroughly disapprove of duels. If a man should
            challenge me, I would take him kindly and forgivingly by the
            hand and lead him to a quiet place and kill him.</item>
        <item>I was gratified to be able to answer promptly. I said I
            don\'t know.</item>
        <item>If you pick up a starving dog and make him prosperous, he
            will not bite you. This is the principal difference between
            a dog and a man.</item>
        <item>If you tell the truth you don\'t have to remember anything.
        </item>
        <item>In Paris they simply stared when I spoke to them in
            French; I never did succeed in making those idiots
            understand their language.</item>
        <item>In religion and politics, people\'s beliefs and convictions
            are in almost every case gotten at second hand, and without
            examination.</item>
        <item>In the first place, God made idiots. That was for
            practice. Then he made school boards.</item>
        <item>It could probably be shown by facts and figures that there
            is no distinctly American criminal class except Congress.
        </item>
        <item>It is better to deserve honors and not have them than to
            have them and not to deserve them.</item>
        <item>It is better to keep your mouth closed and let people
            think you are a fool than to open it and remove all doubt.
        </item>
        <item>It is curious that physical courage should be so common in
            the world and moral courage so rare.</item>
        <item>It is easier to stay out than get out.</item>
        <item>It usually takes more than three weeks to prepare a good
            impromptu speech.</item>
        <item>It was wonderful to find America, but it would have been
            more wonderful to miss it.</item>
        <item>Just the omission of Jane Austen\'s books alone would make
            a fairly good library out of a library that hadn\'t a book in
            it.</item>
        <item>Keep away from people who try to belittle your ambitions.
            Small people always do that, but the really great make you
            feel that you, too, can become great.</item>
        <item>Let us be thankful for the fools. But for them the rest of
            us could not succeed.</item>
        <item>Let us so live that when we come to die even the
            undertaker will be sorry.</item>
        <item>Most people are bothered by those passages of Scripture
            they do not understand, but the passages that bother me are
            those I do understand.</item>
        <item>My mother had a great deal of trouble with me, but I think
            she enjoyed it.</item>
        <item>Never put off until tomorrow what you can do the day after
            tomorrow.</item>
        <item>New Orleans food is as delicious as the less criminal
            forms of sin.</item>
        <item>Often it does seem a pity that Noah and his party did not
            miss the boat.</item>
        <item>Part of the secret of success in life is to eat what you
            like and let the food fight it out inside.</item>
        <item>Suppose you were an idiot and suppose you were a member of
            Congress. But I repeat myself.</item>
        <item>The best way to cheer yourself is to try to cheer someone
            else up.</item>
        <item>The coldest winter I ever spent was a summer in San
            Francisco.</item>
        <item>The difference between the right word and the almost right
            word is the difference between lightning and a lightning
            bug.</item>
        <item>The human race has one really effective weapon, and that
            is laughter.</item>
        <item>The man who doesn\'t read good books has no advantage over
            the man who can\'t read them.</item>
        <item>The right word may be effective, but no word was ever as
            effective as a rightly timed pause.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>